넌 구름을 몰라
You just don't know cloud,
이 작고, 작고, 엉망인 지역은
this tiny, little, shitty area,
엄청나게 중요해 지고 있어요
which is becoming super important,
그리고 많은 면에서 컴퓨터의 미래가 있다.
and in many ways is the future of computing.
그런 식으로 화가 나긴 했지만 내 말을 이해할 거야
That sort of went south on me, but you understand what I'm saying.
나는 이미 피터 그레고리와 컨설턴트를 소개한 적이 있다.
I've already talked to Peter Gregory about insourcing a consultant.
클라우드 아키텍처를 사용하는 프로그래머와 연락을 했습니다.
I've made contact with a programmer whose cloud architecture
미친 게 틀림없어요 그들은 그를 Carver라고 부른다.
is supposed to be insane. They call him The Carver.
카버 씨? 미국 은행에 침입한 것으로 보이는 검은 모자를 쓴 남자
The Carver? That Black Hat guy who apparently hacked into the Bank of America
그리고 그들의 전체 시스템을 없앴어요, 카버 씨?
and took down their entire system, that The Carver?